Okay so hello everyone in this video let's work with our fetching the response from the
sign up for login pages. So first what I'm going to do is let's go inside of the source
folder and let's make one library folder. Okay so with the LIB what we are going to do
is like we are going to fish the response from our APIs right. So in that case we are going
to make one file which is called as Axios.js right. In the access.js file just import
Axios from Axios okay. So we are going to import Axios from Axios and then we are going
to export Xio's instance okay equal to Axios.create and just go here and we have the base
URL right. From the base URL we are going to just take the response so in our case it
would be HTTP / local host and 5,000 / API. So from this base URL we are going to take the
response and with credentials we are going to set this as true. So this would be the function
okay. So now after this since we have to also make another like we have to manage the state
of our application also right like for example when we are going to sign in to our one
like sign up to our one particular as a one particular user. Then in that case we have
to know like whether the user has particular user has logged in or not. So we are going
to do that we are global state management. That's why we have installed the juice stand
right. So go inside of the source folder and make one more file or one more folder to be
precise which is called as auth. So now in the auth okay so maybe it's not auth rename it's
store actually inside of the store let's make one file which is auth store.js we are going
to implement juice stand in this one which is going to be for the global state management.
So import we are going to just take this from the juice stand and now we are going to export
const a function like auth store and we are going to create one. So set and then inside of it we
have to know whether the logged in user whether the user has logged in or not. So for the first
time it would be null okay. So initial state would be null because we don't know whether the user
has logged in or not. That's why I have set this logged in log user to the null and then we are
going to just take this sign up and sign up would be a sync and it is going to take up some data
okay. So and inside of this we are simply implementing the try and cache block okay. So try and
cache block hey one thing before connecting the like frontend and backend we needed to do one thing.
So we need to actually get get that cost to implement. So the cost is actually one middle
where which is going to connect the frontend with the back end. So we have to go for navigate
to our back end folder and inside of the back end folder we are going to the source and we are
going to check whether the course package is installed or not. So let's go here. So inside of this
let's close the frontend folder and inside of this we will have this source and in this source
let's see package.json let's see this okay. So the course is not implemented that's why it will
cause some issue. So control C we will close the frontend we will quit the frontend server and now
let's navigate to the back end site. So Siri double do double dash double dot sorry. Now CD back end
so go to the back end folder. So we are back end folder now we are going to install one package
which is called as course. Since we have to implement that one also right. So we have implemented
like installed the course package. So as we can see the course is implemented sorry installed. So
now go to the app.js inside of the app.js what we are going to do is since it's a middle where
we are going to place it in that place only so app.use inside of the app.use we are going to
just say that okay course. So for this course we are going to set the values for origin
it is going to be our frontend website like our frontend so this URL. So it would be STTP
double slash local host and then 5173 and then the credentials credentials
credentials would be true. So that is the change which we are going to make as a middle where
because it's important we are going to connect the frontend and the back end. So that's why
so in the frontend let's go to the source and now let's go to this store and authstore.js
after this this sign up right. So we have one this created and along with that we need to
have this sign up. So sign up async data once again.
So it would be like sign up and it would be async and then data
the data would come and we will put that data in the try and catch block
so that if any kind of error happens we are going to log it. So error wait a second.
Let's remove this const res equals to a wait axios instance and for this axios instance we have set
set logged in user so log to user to be whatever the response that comes from that side.
So response dot data and also for the catch block we are going to just say that console dot log
server error.